Hello friends, I am Doctor
Se. The first company we are going to discuss
is Itta. Friends, this is a
company belonging to LTT Industries.
Sachin works on research and development.
This company's
majority of sales comes
from transportation and we will be able to see the effect of this
in this as well. If we
look at the sales, in H1, where the sales were 20%, the
profit was 15% and the margin was
14%. By the time we come to Part V,
these sales improved by 23%, the
profit improved by 27% and the margin
improved by 15%. So, we can say
that by the end of this year, we will get a sales improvement of 25%, a
profit improvement of 25%
and a margin of 15%. Friends, according to this,
our 91% of 2022,
we will achieve
21% of the revenue of all the IT related and technology related companies by the end of this year.  It has been
around 22-25, but why is LDS low
because its majority of revenue came
from transportation and transportation was
in muted growth for the last five to six years. Now we will see that as there is growth
in transportation,
we will see improvement in this yield as well.
Its yield at this time is
around 3.18%, friends, if we look
at its technical chart, then it is around 3000, or
better, around 65, and our short term
target should be around 5000-5100,
and in this way, we can keep 2% in the company right now,
and why not keep 2%
in our portfolio, when it is investing
in future, that is, it is investing
in Internet of Things, it is
investing in whatever is related to IT, so it is a
good company, we should
keep it in our portfolio. The
next company is ICICI Lombard General
Insurance. ICICI is a
listed company, it has its
own standard on listed general
insurance.  It is the only major company that
comes in the top three. If we look at all the general
insurance companies, if we look at it,
like you can see in HDFC Life also, the
last two years have been bad for
general insurance. Similarly, the last two years have been bad for general insurance.
Here, in sales, we
saw in H1 that the profit was 24%, and the margin was 21%
and the margin was 11%. Now, if we divide
it into quarters, we saw that
we got a sales growth of 29%, a profit of 18%
and a margin of about 10%. You
can expect that by 2023 we will get a
sales growth of 30%, a profit of 30% and a
margin of 31-10%. What does this mean? The
upside of 32 in 2022 was 32, we
expect that this year the
surplus will be 34, which means its shares are
getting cheaper because there is a problem. If we
talk about insurance companies, then from 1100
A good one of 1300 is also running in its bang range,
our shortcut will be 1790 and this
company should have 2% population. The next
company we will talk about is
Godrej Consumer Products, an
Indian multinational company which is
working in personal products.
We saw a huge hit
in the last quarter where we got 8% sales growth,
profit - 17% and margin of 11%. So we can say
that forward it means by the
end of this year there is 6% less sales
growth, profit growth of 10% and
margin of 13%. Friends, the
towers etc. of other companies got a good hit there,
but Godrej, for example, in
its new update, it has
said that because of its
personal products,
personal care products,
they did not get double digital in that, so we
can expect that Godrej is
not going to make lifetime high profit this year, so
forward DPS which was 17 in 2022  We
expect it to be 16 this year,
still it is 29, poverty is 57, this is a
bit expensive, at this price
we are
getting a result of 1.8%, if we look at the technical, then
it has a good bike price around 732,
Abhishek, those who are doing SIP on it
can slowly dominate the correction,
our short term target will be around 1102
and
we should allocate 1.5% of Consumer Protective Company in our portfolio.
Titan Company
is a company that manufactures discreet products and its sales belonging to the gems and
jewellery sector
were 68% in H1, profit -
631% and margin was 6%. The industry was affected.
If we look at water vans, we will see that it has a
sensational sales growth of 172% and
profit growth of ₹4000 plus. But
friends, all this is visible because it is due to
a low margin. Okay, we
can expect that
it will improve by the end of this year and we can expect a sales growth of 50%
and a profit growth of 65% here.
Its margin has been
consistently maintained at 8%.
We can expect the same margin of 8% by the end of the year. According to this,
we can expect a forwarding DPS of 24. According to this, the
UPS of 2022 was 24. We can expect a
power DPS of 40, friends, which the
company is currently  According to the update given by them,
they have got almost double digital growth in Water 2
and this is very positive right
now because in the coming time,
pesticides are going to come. Mains Navratri
1.65%
Friends, if we look at its technical,
this price between 1064 to 64 to 1250
is a good price and in the coming 2 to 4
years, we can make a profit of up to 5%
between 3500 to 4200.
This kind of company
should have a share of 3% in our portfolio Friends, the
next company is
Madrasan Sumi which now wants to be known
as Samvardhan Madrasan. Samvardhan Madrasan
International Limited is the largest auto parts
selling company. The Indian
listed company has pressed. The most
special thing about this company is that it has
maintained its sales till now, but because it is
directly related to the auto sector, it
also felt the average phase of auto,
in H1 it increased its sales by 30%.  It
happens that the margin was maintained at 2%,
profit was made and the margin can be made 1%, it is a
bit big but friends, this is the
sector which is taking a U-turn right now,
in the coming time, it is growing like A and so on, so it is
expected to get good growth from here, so our forecast hips
2000 which is last year's 2012,
we expect that by the end of this year
we will get an upside of 2.8, its forward P
is 28 and we expect powered P to be 36,
its
forward yield at this price is 2.6%, friends, if
we look at the technical,
if we get it between 69 and 6289, then it will be a good black
price and our short term target will
be 140, it has to be given only 5% weight in the portfolio because it
is a company, along with this, there
is another point here that it has recently shown its
once to be bonus, meaning it has just
given its bonus to its
investors because  Friends, the next company
is Madrasan Sumi, Madrasan Samvardhan, which was
spun off from you. This company
means MSWI. This was
recently spun off from here this year,
hence we do not have its historical
data, but annually it gave sales of 36%, there was a
growth of 62% in profit and
its margin is very good than its parent company.
Its quality is also
gathered from its parent company. Friends, it is
currently doing its wiring only in India
and its main business focus is on
making high voltage wiring hardness.
We got the result of this in water van, there was
50% sales, 59% profit and 8%
marksheet. We can expect that
till the end we will get 50% sales daily,
50% profit, box payer and 7%
margin. So according to this, the
appx time of the van was obtained in 2022, we
can expect that the forward DPS will be almost 10%.
Still  It is not available but what happens is
that the return of this company should be
almost around 25-30 because it belongs to
growth industries
but its forward piece
and at this time
2.3% technical we see if we
want to invest in this company, we
keep a target of 123, Portugal, we can give it up
to 1%
company, it is
info system, it is a new sector company, this
sector has just opened in India, the
regulations related to mapping have changed,
due to this new companies have just started working well in this sector,
we have got
some results in 9 months, in 9 months its
sales were 36%, profit is 63% what is the
margin of 45%, in the first quarter
we saw that sales came in at 14%
and margin was 37%, we
can express that its forward
year end sales will be 20%, profit will be 5%
and margin will be 38%,
its app which was 16%, we
can expect  By the end of the year, we got an app of Rs 17.
Friends, this
belongs to the company, it has also started becoming
our favorite, it is available on the exchange, at this
time its yield is 1.2% and
technically,
if we get to buy it between Rs 1000, 1100 to 1250, it will be
a good range
and its target is that
its 1% allocation in the portfolio will be
sufficient. Thank you sir, thank you, the
profit team has done
research on many companies and
this was not a hard work but it will take full
time and you have also taken out time from your busy
schedule and done all the research, for this
I would like to thank you
and these companies are important, some are
from the emerging sector and some
are established companies, so I would
like to take an expert opinion on this company so that our all India viewers can
also get a good view, so I
would request that on this good company, they should send
their expert opinion on the
emerging sector, the industry of tomorrow.  It is
related to some automation, which has to do
with automobile companies,
so do it a little less in the fast 5 years,
but we do it strongly in this,
and what is needed, it is in correction mode,
definitely we should accumulate,
insurance, we have already told you that they are at
second place in India's fastest growing sector, so whether it is
life insurance or
general or essential, and this strong group will give on
both the insurances, the
sales brain is strong in both, this also
in correction, do a plate
in a moment, since India has started the
Swachh Abhiyan, I think the
garbage collector must be coming to every house, blowing garbage, you will come out, there are still
many diseases as
compared to other countries, but still this thing has helped
your business, that too, so the health
related
copy, the update they have given is a
good group, but we will not expect good growth in the near term, what is the
full update they have given,
brother, I think they have given 18% growth for the
quarter, 18% right,
so double digital means
and another very important thing is that
they have added stores in almost all their segments.
25%
stores have been added in jewellery, 28 stores have been set for 23 watches, in that
too 38% stores have been added, which
means everyone is saving money,
what is this, the retail boom in India, you
know that the income of an average Indian which
is 2000 dollars today, is bound to become ₹10000, so
people are bound to spend,
so this is a wealth creator, it is
still in the correction board, attention
should be paid, Madrasan and Madrasan Wiring,
both of these are related to auto, so they are affected,
we can see the group in the coming time,
I think Madrasan has also opened a Morocco, it is just a
mistake, the polymer business there
which is used in blood door panels, to
make all those products,
now in India, this is a very great industry of the coming times,
this new age industry,
this business, earlier in India, I mean, what
can we do with it, it was not even open, the
government opened this business some time back  If
mapping can be done then it seems to be a bright future for the company,
it will be used in many different emerging sectors, the Locha
Stick policy has just come, see it will be beneficial
and even now they have started a new mapping,
Ramayan Nithik, what is that,
people will think Ramayan Methi means it is
related to Ramayan, is the picture coming now,
Adi Purush is after Ramayan, it is
not like that, in heritage they will
tell about the maps of 5000 years ago in their Ramayan, so it is a very
optimistic plan, this will also
increase their business and this
mapping will benefit many industries, so logistics mapping,
all this is going to be given to them by a group of 15 Bisht,
focus, it is breaking right now, it is in correction, in
my opinion it should be done in 1 minute, right, so
wonderful presentation by you wait by